克鲁克路
克鲁克路  气球
别开枪
Do not fire that weapon.
擦
Shit.
看看这里有什么
Look at what we got here.
亲爱的  瞧瞧你
Oh, honey, look at you.
你糟透了
You're a damn mess.
该死
Damn it.
擦
Shit.
能借我一用吗
Can I borrow that a sec?
谢谢
Thanks.
我可不会漏过你
Oh, I'm not leaving you out.
车厢后面有抹布
There's some rags in the back.
怎么了
What?
-怎么了  -我之前没见过
- What? - Never seen that before.
我见你做过同样的事
I've seen you do the same thing.
你笑了
You smiled.
你刚在笑
You were smiling.
我是
Well, I'm the...
世界上最幸运的人
luckiest guy in the world.
不如你帮我推开汽车吧
How about you help me with one of these cars?
路还长着呢
We got some miles to go.
m 325 0 l 355 0 l 332 47 l 354 47 l 399 136 l 369 136 l 328 53 l 288 136 l 257 136 l 325 0 m 467 0 l 497 0 l 474 47 l 496 47 l 541 136 l 511 136 l 470 53 l 430 136 l 399 136 l 467 0 m 545 1 l 583 1 l 583 14 l 568 14 l 568 19 l 583 19 l 583 30 l 568 30 l 568 34 l 599 34 l 599 30 l 583 30 l 583 19 l 599 19 l 599 14 l 583 14 l 583 1 l 611 1 b 616 1 622 6 622 10 l 622 36 l 652 0 l 678 0 l 644 41 l 622 41 l 622 47 l 596 47 l 597 54 l 625 54 l 625 68 l 541 68 l 541 54 l 572 54 l 571 47 l 545 47 l 545 1 m 583 72 l 583 85 l 569 85 l 569 90 l 598 90 l 598 85 l 583 85 l 583 72 l 611 72 b 615 72 621 78 621 82 l 653 44 l 678 44 l 644 86 l 621 86 l 621 103 l 597 103 l 597 136 l 570 136 l 564 126 l 562 136 l 542 136 l 548 107 l 568 107 l 565 121 l 571 121 l 571 103 l 547 103 l 547 72 l 583 72 m 600 107 l 620 107 l 624 124 l 653 89 l 679 89 l 642 136 l 615 136 l 618 132 l 606 132 l 600 107 m 689 0 l 716 0 l 721 15 l 732 15 l 732 30 l 718 56 l 731 56 l 735 100 l 721 100 l 717 59 l 714 64 l 714 136 l 693 136 l 693 79 l 676 79 l 707 30 l 679 30 l 679 15 l 694 15 l 689 0 m 738 0 l 804 0 b 807 0 813 6 813 9 l 813 87 l 794 87 l 794 14 l 756 14 l 756 87 l 763 77 l 763 21 l 787 21 l 787 91 l 798 91 l 798 120 l 820 120 l 812 136 l 778 136 l 778 90 l 748 136 l 723 136 l 756 87 l 738 87 l 738 0 m 257 151 l 275 151 l 297 182 l 319 151 l 337 151 l 304 197 l 304 227 l 290 227 l 290 197 l 257 151 m 337 151 l 355 151 l 377 182 l 399 151 l 417 151 l 384 197 l 384 227 l 370 227 l 370 197 l 337 151 m 425 192 l 447 192 b 445 181 427 181 425 192 l 410 192 b 414 162 458 162 462 192 l 462 206 l 425 206 b 425 210 429 212 433 213 l 462 213 l 462 227 l 433 227 b 412 227 408 203 410 192 m 462 151 l 532 151 l 532 165 l 504 165 l 504 227 l 489 227 l 489 165 l 462 165 l 462 151 m 580 172 l 580 186 l 549 186 b 543 186 543 192 549 192 l 565 192 b 589 192 589 227 565 227 l 532 227 l 532 213 l 565 213 b 570 213 570 206 565 206 l 549 206 b 524 206 524 172 549 172 l 580 172 m 592 213 l 606 213 l 606 227 l 592 227 l 592 213 m 639 172 l 665 172 l 665 186 l 639 186 b 623 186 623 213 639 213 l 665 213 l 665 227 l 639 227 b 603 227 603 172 639 172 m 700 184 b 722 184 722 215 700 215 l 700 229 b 740 229 740 170 700 170 b 660 170 660 229 700 229 l 700 215 b 680 215 680 184 700 184 m 737 172 l 782 172 b 803 172 813 177 813 198 l 813 228 l 799 228 l 799 198 b 799 186 793 187 782 187 l 782 228 l 768 228 l 768 187 l 752 187 l 752 228 l 737 228 l 737 172
m 115 64 l 115 35 l 171 0 l 177 0 l 133 46 l 143 52 l 179 0 l 184 0 l 159 63 l 229 107 l 229 182 l 145 96 l 135 122 l 207 227 l 137 227 l 115 172 l 115 93 l 126 76 l 115 64 l 104 76 l 115 93 l 115 172 l 93 227 l 23 227 l 95 122 l 84 96 l 0 182 l 0 107 l 70 63 l 45 0 l 50 0 l 87 52 l 97 46 l 52 0 l 59 0 l 115 35
m 20 0 l 209 0 b 218 0 229 11 229 20 l 229 209 b 229 218 218 228 209 228 l 20 228 b 11 228 0 218 0 209 l 0 20 b 0 11 11 0 20 0
本字幕由人人影视字幕组翻译
禁止用作任何商业盈利行为
翻译  鸟の森
翻译  蘑菇
翻译  Reginamoon
翻译  重案组李Sir
翻译  小饭
翻译  CS小明漫画家
翻译/校对  冰蓝
翻译/校对  送小孩
翻译/校对  卫老哥
时间轴  雪贵人
时间轴  涛涛  森の鸟
后期  、青衣
特效/后期  吉吉
总监  送小孩
行尸走肉
第四季  第十一集
你对我这件超级舒适又好看的衬衫
Do you have something to say about my extremely comfortable
有意见吗
and attractive shirt?
不不  它看起来很棒
No, no, no. It looks great.
你没扣好...
Oh, you missed a...
真希望我们有豆奶
I wish we had some soy milk.
认真的吗
Seriously?
是认真的
Yes, seriously.
你喝过吗
Have you ever tried it?
我三年级时的最好朋友
My best friend in third grade,
他对牛奶过敏
he was allergic to dairy.
他每天午餐时都会带上豆奶
And every day he would bring this soy stuff to lunch.
-我喝过  -然后呢
- I tried it. - And?
-我吐了  -别说瞎话
- I threw up. - Oh, yeah, right.
好吧  好吧  我差点吐了
All right, all right. I almost threw up.
但我觉得很恶心
But I was like, ugh.
恶心死了
It was so gross.
说真的  我宁愿喝奶粉
I mean, literally, I would rather have powdered milk
也不愿意再喝那种东西了
than to have to drink that stuff again.
我宁愿喝朱迪思的婴儿奶粉...
I would rather have Judith's formula--
我去把书看完
I'm gonna go finish my book.
还剩几章
I have a couple chapters left.
谢谢你
Thank you.
我听到他在里面笑
I heard him laughing in there.
我都快忘了他的笑声是什么样了
Almost forgot what that sounded like.
我不能同时当他的严父和益友
I can't be his father and his best friend.
他需要你
He needs you.
我知道你一下子很难接受
I know that's a lot to throw at you.
所以如果你需要休息一下
So if you're ever feeling like you need a break...
我不想再休息了
I'm done taking breaks.
你有什么计划
So what's the plan?
这里
This place,
是家
is it home
还是暂时的避风港
or just a stop along the way?
我们...
Well, let's--
先在这里住下再商量吧
let's just stay here while we figure it out.
我们需要更多的补给品
Well, we'll need more supplies.
我跟卡尔去找
I'll go with Carl and get some.
我也去
I'll come, too.
你昨天还昏迷不醒
You were unconscious yesterday.
-今天醒了  -我们需要你恢复体力
- I'm awake today. - We need you strong.
休息一下
Just rest.
再休息一天
Just one more day.
你们会去多久
How long you think you'll be?
装满几个袋子  应该不会太久
Fill a couple bags, shouldn't be too long.
现在是八点一刻
It's 8:15 now.
我们中午回来
We'll be back by noon.
好的  你听她的话
All right, you follow her lead.
懂了吗
You understand?
你没事吧
Everything okay?
没事  我只是
Yeah, I'm just...
饿了
hungry.
好
All right.
几小时后见
I'll see you in a couple hours.
找到好东西了吗
Find anything good?
糖果
Candy bars?
漫画书
Comic books?
乳酪布丁呢
Crazy Cheese?
看  乳酪布丁
Bam, Crazy Cheese.
还是密封的呢
Found it still sealed and everything.
我做个好人  让你吃第一口
Now I'll be nice and let you have the first pull.
不了  谢谢
No, thanks.
真的
Are you sure?
我没事
I'm fine.
你看起来不像没事
You don't seem fine.
我只是累了
I'm just tired.
好吗
Okay?
对不起
I'm sorry.
我不太擅长逗你这个年龄的男孩笑
I'm not very good at making boys your age laugh.
我笑了
I was laughing.
在心里笑
Inside.
小宝宝觉得我很逗
Toddlers find me funny.
两三岁的
Two, three-year-olds.
小宝宝是什么意思
What do you mean toddlers?
我有过一个三岁的儿子
I had a three-year-old son
而他觉得我超级搞笑
and he happened to find me extremely funny.
我们需要食物  电池  水
We need food, batteries, water,
分清主次
in that order.
为什么你从没告诉过我你有过孩子
Why didn't you ever tell me you had a kid?
他叫什么
What was his name?
你有其他孩子吗
Did you have any others?
你结过婚吗
Were you married?
好吧
Okay.
我每次只回答一个问题
I'll answer one question at a time,
每进一个房间回答一次
one room at a time,
而且必须在我们确认屋内安全之后
and only after we've cleared it.
-不要  对不起  -你是个撒谎的懦夫
- No, I'm sorry. - You're a lying coward.
你不会变的
That's all you'll ever be.
不  求你了  我很抱歉
No, please, I'm sorry.
别这么做  求你了
Don't do this, please.
你他妈对我说什么了
What the hell'd you say to me?
-我说别这么做  -这不关你的事
- I said don't do this. - This ain't your business.
-我很抱歉  伙计  -你闭嘴吧
- I'm sorry, man. -Aw, shut up.
我真的很抱歉  不  不要
I'm so sorry. No, don't.
我会动手的
It's gonna happen.
我们能和好的  求你了
We can work this out. Please,
-别这么做  -我不会停手
- Don't do this. - It's gonna happen.
不  不  不要  求你了
No, no, no, please.
拜托不要  求你了
Please don't. Please!
-你会搞定他吗  -是的
- You plan on finishing the job? - Yeah.
我耳朵都要聋了
I'm getting an earache
我就知道他会让他惨叫
and I know he's just gonna let his ass squeal.
就凭他做过的事  这男的活该流血
After what he did, the man deserves to bleed.
你们想的话就都留在下面
Y'all stay down there if you want.
我们今晚就住这儿了
This will be our abode for the evening.
把你的烂摊子收拾干净  哈利
Clean up your mess, Harley.
你儿子叫什么
What was your son's name?
我说了检查后再说
I said after.
这其实是两间分开的房间
Well, these are actually two separate rooms
而我们已经检查了那间  所以
and we already cleared that one, so...
安德烈
Andre.
他叫安德烈・安东尼
His name was Andre Anthony.
你去看看那儿有没有藏着饼干
Make sure there isn't a box of cookies hiding in there.
你还有其他孩子吗
Did you have any other kids?
朋友  注意游戏规则
Rules of the game, my friend.
所以呢
So?
你有吗
Did you?
你知道吗  你真适合当间谍
You know, you could be a spy.
或者是警察
Or a cop.
没有
No.
一个孩子对我而言就够了
One was enough for me.
安德烈就是个小麻烦  像你一样
And Andre was a handful, like you.
这个走廊算一个房间吗
Does this hallway count as a room?
假如你能在这里找到物资就算
If you can find something we can use.
我只找到这个
This is the only thing I could find.
这算吗
Does it count?
理论上算
Technically, yes.
那么
So?
过去多久了
How long has it been?
那事发生在...
It happened after--
发生在灾变之后
you know, after everything happened.
我爸爸知道吗
Does my dad know?
我从没告诉过他
Never told him.
在刚刚告诉你之前
Never told anyone
我从没告诉过任何人
till just now.
我会为你保密
Your secret is safe with me.
其实也不算什么秘密
It's not really a secret.
我还是会保密
It's still safe with me.
别打扰  梅梅在睡觉
梅梅
米琼恩
Michonne?
没事吧
Everything okay?
没事
Yeah, it's fine.
那里有孩子吗
There's a baby in there.
是条狗
It's a dog.
我爸让我给她取名字
My dad let me name her.
也许
Maybe--
也许她跟安德烈在同一个地方
maybe her and Andre are together somewhere.
走吧
Come on.
快中午了
It's almost noon.
要是晚了  你爸爸会担心的
Your dad will wonder where we are if we're late.
喂
Yo.
舒服吗
Comfy?
你把我弄醒就为了问我舒不舒服吗
You waking me up to see if I'm comfortable?
我想躺会儿
I want to lie down.
这层还有两个卧室呢
Two other bedrooms up here to choose.
那是小孩的床
Them's kids' beds.
我要这张
I want this one.
-已经被我占了  -我可不管
- It's claimed. - I didn't hear it.
你换个地方去占吧
You gonna have to lay claim somewhere else.
伦
Len!
伦  住手
Len, stop!
Stop, Len!
-住手  -休想
- Stop! - Hell, no.
住手
Stop!
床归我了  混蛋
My bed now, jackoff.
别动
Hey, don't move.
喝点水
Here's some water.
我们在哪儿
Where are we?
我不知道
I don't know.
一离开监狱我们就跟行尸干上了
We were fighting biters and you passed out
然后你晕倒了
right after we left the prison.
我不知道怎么办
I didn't know what to do.
坐在卡车后面似乎比走路更安全
The back of the truck seemed safer than the side of the road.
路上有大巴吗
Did we pass a bus?
我们有没有路过一辆大巴
On the road, did we pass a bus?
有
Yeah.
你看到什么了
What did you see?
他们都死了
They were all dead.
我们路过多久了
How long since we passed it?
三小时
Three hours.
停车
Hey, stop the truck.
该死的  快停车
Hey, numbnuts, stop the truck.
快停车
Stop the truck!
你要去哪儿
Where the hell are you going?
他要去哪儿
Where the hell is he going?
我不知道你的女伙伴有没有告诉你
I don't know what your lady friend's told you
我们这次任务的特殊性
about the special nature of the mission we're on,
但我们赶时间
but this shit is time-sensitive
而且已经比计划晚了
and we're already way behind schedule.
所以你马上转身给我回车上去
So I need you to turn your ass around and get back in the truck.
-我必须得走  -你们俩好像
- I gotta go. - It seems like neither one of you's
完全不了解
been paying close enough attention
我们现在的糟糕处境
to the hell on earth we've been living in.
那我就告诉你怎么才能避免
So let me tell you how to best avoid
变成那种行尸走肉
winding up just another dead-alive prick.
找到强大而且志同道合的伙伴
You find some strong, like-minded comrades
然后不论发生什么  都待在一起
and you stay stuck together like wet on water.
我们需要人
We need people.
多多益善  我们相互依赖  伙计
The more the better. We need each other, partner.
即便有这么多装备  你也不可能撑过一晚
Even with all that gear on your shoulder, you won't last a night.
你自己肯定不行
Not by yourself.
我愿意冒险
I'll take my chances.
我必须坚持
I'm gonna have to insist
让你留下
that you hold the hell up.
不管你信不信
All right, believe it or not,
全人类的命运也许就取决于此了
the fate of the entire damn human race might depend on it.
你在说什么
What the hell are you talking about?
这家伙是谁
Who is this guy?
我是亚伯拉罕・福特中士
I'm Sergeant Abraham Ford.
他们是我的同伴
And these are my companions
罗西塔・埃斯皮诺萨和尤金・伯特博士
Rosita Espinosa and Dr. Eugene Porter.
我们的任务是把尤金送到华府
We're on a mission to get Eugene to Washington, DC.
尤金是科学家
Eugene's a scientist
他知道行尸遍地的真正原因
and he knows exactly what caused this mess.
好吧
All right.
怎么回事
So what happened?
这是机密
It's classified.
他一直在用卫星电话
He'd been talking to the muckety-mucks in Washington
和华盛顿高层保持联系
on his satellite phone.
但过去的几个星期里
The past couple weeks,
没有人接电话了
nobody's been picking up on the other end.
我们看到了你之前是如何对付行尸的
We saw how you handled those corpses back there.
我们需要你的帮助
We could use your help.
抱歉
Sorry.
之前我们不得不离开那条路
I had to get us off that road.
你晕过去了  我们也没有子弹了
You were passed out, we were out of bullets.
但是我知道怎么回到大巴那里
But I know how to get back to that bus.
我把每个转弯都记下来了
I wrote down every turn.
我会把你带回去的  我可以的  好吗
I will get you back, I can, okay?
她会去那找我
That's where she'd go to find me.
-我要去那  -那是浪费时间
- That's where I'm gonna go. - It's a waste of time.
塔拉告诉了我发生了什么
Tara told us what went down.
你找到你妻子的可能性为零
There is zero chance you will ever find your wife again.
不管是死是活
Alive or dead.
因为  抱歉这样说
Mainly because, sorry to tell you,
她死了
she's gone.
你没必要也去送死
No need for you to die, too.
走吧
Now come on.
回车上去  做点有意义的事
Get back in the truck. Do something with your life.
当我们...
When the people we...
爱的人死...
we love kick...
当他们消失时
well, they disappear.
不意味着你也要跟着消失
Doesn't mean you've got to go out that way, too.
她还活着  我会找到她的
She's alive and I'm gonna find her.
狗娘养的
You son of a bitch!
-嘿  -亚伯拉罕
- Hey, hey, hey! - Abraham!
放开他
Hey, get off him.
住手
Come on.
别这样  亚伯拉罕
You don't want this, Abraham.
放开我
Let me go!
-亚伯拉罕  -住手
- Abraham! - Stop!
-住手  -亚伯拉罕
- Hey! - Abraham!
快住手
Hey, get--
别打了  过来
Hey, hey, hey! Come here!
住手
Stop!
尤金
Eugene!
别开枪  该死
Stop firing, damn it!
别开枪了  我们得去拿武器
Stop firing! We need to get our weapons.
别管他了
Leave 'em!
给我支枪
Hey, give me a gun.
Give me a gun.
妈蛋
Son of a dick.
托尼  伦  滚下来
Tony, Len, get your asses down here.
听见没有
Yo, you hear me?
快下来
Claim, Claim, Claim!
闭上臭嘴  我要睡觉
Shut the hell up. I'm trying to sleep.
有个女的住在这
There's a woman shacking up in here.
-什么  -你下来看看
- Say what? - Come on down.
-漂亮吗  -现在先别撸
- She hot? - Don't grab your pecker just yet.
她没在这
She ain't here.
你们瞎嚷嚷什么呢
What the hell you hollering about?
找到了她的衬衫
Found her shirt.
肯定是今天早上才洗的
Must have washed it this morning.
-好香啊  -你们找到了衬衫
- Smells good. - Oh, you found a shirt?
她搞不好已经离开很久了
She could be miles away by now.
她就没必要费力气
Why'd she go to all the trouble of washing a shirt
洗一件要扔的衬衫
when she's just gonna ditch it?
-她会回来的  -她回来之后  我要第一个上
- She'll be back. - I call first when she gets here.
谁知道她有没有同伴呢
Who knows who else she got with her.
我们得做好万全准备
We need to be ready for anything.
-伦  你去侧面房间  -等一下  我去拿枪
- Len, take the side room. - Hold on, let me get a gun.
我会盯着前厅  你负责另一侧的房间
I'll watch the front den, you've got the other side room.
-我以为托尼负责呢  -托尼跑哪去了
- I thought Tony got that. - Where the hell is Tony?
托尼
Tony!
把他叫起来
Get him the hell up.
我们当时开着卡车执行护送任务
We were running a convoy in one of these.
开上一个沙丘  有个骆驼站在那
Coming up a dune, there's this camel,
看起来像是要吐
looks like it's about to puke.
可能是因为哪个混蛋给它屁股上
Probably because shitbird's packed
驼了大概1.8公斤的C-4炸弹
about four pounds of C-4 up its ass.
我们距离爆炸点也就六米左右
We were within 20 feet of that blast
驼峰炸飞出去了半公里
that sent that animal's hump half a klick into the desert.
然后我们还能开车回去
And we drove home.
所以你跟我说说你到底做了什么
So you tell me how in the holy hell
才能让这卡车抛锚
did you possibly kill this truck?
高度兴奋的状态
A fully amped-up state
和对速射武器的无知
and an ignorance of rapid-firing weapons.
这是你的吗
Is this yours?
车子坏了我很遗憾
Sorry about your ride.
希望你们能到达华府
Hope you guys make it to Washington.
等等我
Wait for me.
我们他妈的还能干什么
What the hell else are we gonna do?
去华府啊
Go to Washington.
拯救世界啊
Fix the whole damn world!
那条路安全  北边就难说了
That way's clear. Who knows what's north.
我们先跟着他们  找到车再离开
We'll find another vehicle. We'll go with them until we do.
相信我  我比你聪明
Trust me. I'm smarter than you.
拜托
Come on.
-挡住它  -奶奶的
- Stop her! - Son of bitch.
杀了它  杀了它
Kill her! Kill her!
走  走
Go! Go!
不得不说
Got to hand it to him.
这小子真坚决
He's a persistent son of a bitch.
我知道你为什么跟随他了
I get why you're following him.
你很忠心
You're loyal.
你是个好人
You're a good person.
我喜欢
I like it.
但我们要做的事
But what we're doing--
我不知道该怎么说
I don't know how else to say it--
拯救世界
saving the world is just--
更为重要
is just more important.
就算他找到妻子
I mean, even if he does find his wife,
那又怎样
so what?
如果我们不把尤金送到华府
How long do you think they'll live happily ever after
你觉得他们能安稳生活多久
if we don't get Eugene up to Washington?
你以为我跟着格伦
You think because I'm following Glenn,
就说明我是个好人吗
that makes me a good person?
我不是好人
I'm not.
你是好人
You're good.
你根本不了解我
You don't know anything about me.
正如我也不了解你为什么要去华府
Just like I don't know anything about why you're going to Washington.
我知道尤金为什么去
I get why Eugene's going.
他是唯一一个知道如何终结这一切的人
He's the only one that knows how to end this.
而罗西塔是因为爱你  她会永远伴你左右
And Rosita, she loves you. She'd follow you anywhere.
但你为什么同意
But why the hell you agreed
带他穿越大半个国家...
to drive him halfway across the country...
我想拯救世界就这么难相信吗
Is that hard to believe, I want to save the world?
仅仅因为你是个好人吗
Because you're a good person?
你不用告诉我真正原因
You don't have to tell me why.
但也别骗我
Just don't lie to me.
乳酪布丁
Crazy Cheese?
你怎么看
What do you think?
我们去吧
Let's go.
去吧
避难所和社区  欢迎所有人
抵达就能活命